Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
(LOUD DANCE MUSIC THUMPING)
Hey, where you been?
Just getting the mail.
- What's for dinner?
- Champagne and caviar.
BOY 1: Oh, shit,
what'd I get?
This is you in the middle.
BOY 2: What are those,
new kicks?
Yeah, I think so.
BOY 1: - Yo, 10 minutes, Call of Duty.
- You're on.
BOY 1: - It's on, bitch.
- Hey, Kyle.
Look what some creep sent me.
What's going on, Princess?
This is you.
What's up, kid?
That's you.
Kinda feel like stilettos.
(VIBRATOR BUZZING)
Seriously, Kyle?
I'm in the middle of a show right now.
I'm sorry. I'm just bringing your stuff.
I went to the post office
for you, come on.
That's sick.
All right, who wants to go
private tonight, huh?
Come on, guys.
Keep me entertained.
Just tell me what you're into
and we can go private.
Ball gags.
Yes, Sassy, I'm 18 years old.
Is this your first time
going private?
Whatever you're
in the mood for.
You like my diamond, huh?
Come on, Sassy.
What are you, some sort of chick?
Huh?
I love chicks.
No, I have, actually,
I have lots of hot mommies and daddies.
Did you see my wish list?
That's how you can reward me.
Very clever.
You ask a lot
of questions, girl.
Come on, baby,
what do you want?
What do you want me to do, huh?
Do you want me to jack off for you?
Is that it?
Oh, my God.
You want me to touch myself?
What are you in the mood for?
So you don't.
You don't wanna see me jack off
or play with these toys
or anything?
You really just wanna...
You just wanna chat.
Boo!
Fucking muscle heads.
- All the veins popping out of his biceps.
- Dude!
- Yeah, but did you see...
- That was good, man.
This is awesome.
So fucked up, man.
Here he goes.
He's gonna get it.
- That's ours!
- It's ours? It's ours.
- Can I help you? You sure?
- Yeah.
(LAUGHING) Oh, my God!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
The fuck you looking at?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
MAN ON WEBSITE: Don't do this at home
'cause it's really, really dangerous.
And really, really stupid.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
Is that real?
That's nuts!
This is a job, man. I put you in charge
of these stores and nothing's happening.
Do you have any
kind of answer for me?
I'm really tired
of this shit, man.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
CINDY: Dr. Borland.
Hi.
Really.
Well, we can try again
our next cycle, right?
Thanks, Doctor.
Hey.
So, um...
Dr. Borland said
we could try again.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Can we talk about that
a little later?
- I'm just running a little late.
- Yeah.
(TAPPING CAR HORN)
NINA: You'd be crazy
not to go for this Internet story.
You gotta remind me again.
Kid. Online.
Chat room.
I know. Look, I don't get it.
He sits there all day?
No. No.
He goes private with people.
He's a bright kid.
He's probably trapped.
One minute. Nina, it just sounds so dark.
It's more of a feature than what you're used to.
That's what I'm...
- Thank you.
- I'm just...
Look. There are thousands
of kids like this.
(SPEAKING INDISCERNIBLY)
I really think this
could be powerful, you know?
It's got sex, it's got heart.
Just let me try,
and I will not complain
about sitting behind
this desk 24/7
writing those fluff pieces you give me.
Yes, you will.
FRYE: All right.
Dude, I found him. Ben Boyd.
Says he's in 10th grade
at our school.
JASON: - He's in our grade?
- Yeah.
"Music is my passion.
Everything from Sigur Rós to Radiohead."
What the hell is Sigur Rós?
Who knows? What do we write?
Okay. Write...
"Hi, Ben, my name's Jessica.
I go to Ridgewood."
"Sigur Rós is my fave."
Say something about his song.
Okay. Um...
- "I loved your song on your page."
- All right.
- "Your song was so amazing."
- "It touched me. It's amazing."
- "It touched me." That's good.
- "It touched me."
(DOOR OPENING)
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Dad.
Hi, Mr. Dixon.
I almost ran this over, genius.
Uh... I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
- Yeah.
- How was the game?
- Played like Gretzky.
What are you guys doing?
- Homework.
- Reports.
- Homework?
- Homework.
Homework or that?
Homework on that.
- I'm online.
- Okay. You didn't wear that shirt to school?
- I wore this one over it?
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Are you lying?
- Frye, am I lying?
- I was there.
Yeah? All right.
Frye, I only got
chicken for two,
so you got to get
the hell out of my house.
- Kidding, Frye.
- Oh.
It's okay. My dad wants me home, anyway.
All right, good.
I got two cases to get to, so come on.
- Frye, it was good seeing you.
- You, too, sir.
Look at that.
(WHISPERING)
You know how much Daddy loves you?
What's up, Mommy?
Look at that.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
(VOCALIZING MELODY)
The guy's got a non-compete
clause and it's pretty airtight.
I understand that.
What, are they just
gonna sue the guy and ask questions later?
Right. Well, they can't do that.
So, just have him call
McCortland & Partridge
and we'll work something out, okay?
Like a settlement, come on.
Put your fangs away.
All right. Bye.
Hey, kiddo, where's Mom?
Hey, she's upstairs, I think.
What about Mozart?
At his piano. Where else?
Huh.
(PLAYS PIANO)
Now what are you doing?
(CHUCKLES)
Lean Cuisine again?
You really need to mix it up.
I'm a student of the world,
baby.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
Fuck, no. Come on.
Let's go cam-to-cam.
That way I get to see you, too.
This isn't fair, come on.
Don't be shy.
I'm not going to
charge you anything more.
It costs the same price.
Come on.
It's easy,
just click the button.
- Hello?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Wow. You're...
You're really hot.
(NINA CHUCKLES)
That's very sweet.
You're... You're smokin'.
Please. My God.
You could be my little brother.
God, you are...
You're a MILF.
I'm a MILF?
No, maybe you're
not so much a MILF.
Like, you're not a cougar yet,
'cause you're not that old.
- You're like a puma.
- What's a puma?
It's like the step
before a cougar.
That's really depressing.
You know what? Let's play a game.
For a million dollars,
would you fuck a dirty,
smelly, hairy homeless guy?
Oh, my God, no.
- No? For a million dollars?
- No!
- Okay, two million.
- No.
Bullshit. Come on.
Five million. Five million.
Five million? Okay.
(LAUGHS)
You see,
everybody has their price.
Okay, this is what he wrote.
"Hey, thanks for
liking my song."
"I was nervous
about posting it. I know, I'm weird."
(BOTH LAUGH)
- Okay, say...
- Jason.
What's up, Billy?
Say...
- "I think weird is sexy."
- Oh, yeah, that's good.
Perfect. Okay.
- Did he get it?
- He got it.
He's smiling!
Mom, oh, my God,
the f-ing funniest thing happened today.
Abigail, would you
stop that please?
What?
- F-ing. The f-ing thing.
ABBY: - Sorry. Anyway...
- You know that girl Malinda Goodman?
RICH: - No.
Yeah, well, she had, like, this laser
treatment thing, you know, hair removal.
Anyway, there can be this side effect
sometimes where you grow more hair.
(LINDA GASPS)
I know. I swear, the girl
has a fucking beard.
- Hey.
- Sorry.
Okay. That's enough.
Hey, Ben.
Can you please not do that at the table?
He is.
This is an annoying client, that's
what this is. Dad is working.
What is it, your girlfriend?
RICH: His what?
Girlfriend? Ben!
BEN: It's just a friend.
You type away.
Now, is this
a friend from school?
It's from Ridgewood.
Freakwood.
Guys, come on,
you're boring your mother and I.
It's okay, I'm out, anyway.
- What? Come on.
- Yeah. Me, too.
Okay. Well, you're excused, both of you.
- Well, Ben's officially there, huh?
- Where?
He's at that age where
you have to pull every word out of him.
(PHONE BUZZING)
He's 15. Oh.
I gotta take this.
I was 17 before I started talking,
you know? Hey.
Henry, I understand that. Listen,
that's your job, okay? Yeah, exactly.
(INDISCERNIBLE CHATTER)
MAN ON TELEVISION: So what do we talk about?
State Senator Crisswell, who's backing
plans to stop the sign program
and would join a dozen states
to stop using the sign.
(DOG BARKING DISTANTLY)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
- Hey.
DEREK: - Hey.
- How's El Paso?
- Oh, it's great.
Um, have you used
the MasterCard for something?
No.
Well, it got declined.
Did you max it out
or something?
No, of course not.
Is this why you're calling?
Well, yeah.
Yeah. I want to know
why the credit card isn't working.
- I don't know.
- Great.
So now I'm in El Paso
with no credit card.
I'm sure it's a mistake, Derek.
Just call the number
on the back of the card.
- All right. All right, I'll talk to you later.
- Okay.
- Bye.
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
MAN ON TELEPHONE: Can you verify a $5,300
charge at Best Buy yesterday?
That's not possible.
That's crazy.
There's gotta be a mistake.
A charge for $28
at Victoria's Secret two days ago.
Absolutely not!
Okay, Mrs. Hull,
we'll freeze that account.
What the fuck?
Yeah, yeah, well,
listen, I did that.
I talked to the cops, I filled out that
report, and they told me to go...
No, they said because it's under
$10,000, I have to deal with you guys.
And now you're sending me back to
them and they're gonna say...
All right, so,
if you're gonna investigate this,
how am I gonna pay for shit
in the meantime? You...
You guys have my money.
That's it. That's it. That's all I have.
Yes, because my
automatic payments are bouncing right now.
In about a month.
Well, I can't wait a month
for an investigation.
Okay, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'll call you later.
These people are
fucking useless.
What the fuck happened?
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
Dude, dude. There he is.
Dude, send him a message.
FRYE: All right.
What?
Mom said
you were driving me home from school.
No, Tracy drove me today.
Take the bus.
I have my guitar.
That's not getting in my car.
I'm sorry.
He really is a tool, man.
I told him Jessica's mom died.
I think he really feels
fucking sorry for her now.
You told him
that your mom died?
No, Jessica's mom died.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, dude.
You gotta create empathy.
A whole back story.
It's weird, man.
Your mom died. Yes?
Yeah, dude, whatever,
just creating a story.
Okay. All right,
we have lift off.
You ready? I said,
"What are you up to?"
He says,
"Having lunch with friends."
JASON: What a lying
sack of shit, dude. Let me see.
- This is fucking awesome.
- Okay.
"Hey, Ben, are you horny?"
"I always get horny
in the lunch room."
"Makes me wanna
send you a picture."
- "A picture"?
- "A pic."
- He trusts us, we need to step it up a bit.
- That's true.
Which pic would
you call a Jessica?
Oh, my... Mama!
This one? This one?
I'll do this.
- Yes.
- Send.
You sent it?
I sent it.
FRYE: Here we go.
Dude, I think he just
pissed his pants, man!
(BOTH LAUGHING)
"How about
you send me one back?"
(MOANS)
You are amazing.
That was amazing.
(LAUGHS)
- Peter?
- Yeah?
I'm gonna ask you something
and you're going to say yes.
(LAUGHS LOUDLY)
What? What?
Is that what this is about?
(DOG BARKING)
BOY: Nice.
- Yo.
- Hi.
Hi. You Nina?
- So, do you want to sit?
- Yeah, sure.
How's it going?
- Good. Yeah, good.
- Yeah? Good.
Well, anyway thanks
for coming to meet me.
Yeah, of course.
Um...
Let's do this. I know a place
right up the strip here, if you wanna go.
Listen, Kyle, there's something that
I didn't tell you about myself.
What, are you a dude?
(LAUGHS)
No. No. Wait, hang on.
Do I look like I could be a dude?
- No. No.
- Good.
No, I'm just...
I just think your story
is really interesting,
and I was wondering,
I don't know,
if you would let me
interview you.
What, for like a book?
Well, I work for
a small TV station, a news station.
And I'm a reporter.
- The news? You wanna interview me on TV?
- Yeah.
- Smoke? You have a smoke?
- No.
- Not right now, bro. Okay.
- Because you have a really great story.
You have a really great...
It's a really unique,
interesting story,
and I'd love to report it.
Um...
- it's special.
- Wow, I... I don't know. That's...
- Why not, Kyle?
- Really?
This is why you came down here.
No, but you see,
nobody would recognize you
because you'd be in shadow
and your voice would be distorted.
- I think I'm good, you know. Thank you.
- Totally anonymous.
Don't you want
something better than this?
Yeah, I wanted some money.
I came down here, honestly, because I
thought I was gonna get some cash.
And I'm really sorry
that I lied, but I knew you wouldn't...
I just want to get to know you,
so here's my card.
Here's my card.
Just, you just never know.
Call it.
And my e-mail's
on there as well.
Yo, bro, wait up.
Mike Dixon, please.
Hello, my name is Derek Hull,
and I was referred by a Detective Mantos.
Well, I'm calling
regarding a fraud case.
I'll just call again.
I'll call again.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- Hey, good morning.
- Hey.
- Derek? Mike Dixon.
- Yeah, Derek. Derek Hull.
My pleasure. Thank you for coming so early.
I really appreciate it.
How about social
networking sites, you visit those?
Chat rooms, message boards?
No. No. Well,
she spends her life online, but I don't.
CINDY: - I sell my artwork online.
- Thank you.
It's sort of my business.
Well, I go on
a chat site, sometimes.
What kind of chat rooms?
It's a...
It's a support group website.
Well, here's the thing,
someone out there has all your information.
All right,
here's what's gonna happen.
I am gonna clone
your hard drives,
and I'm gonna go through all the
information and the activity
and see if I can figure out
how and when this happened.
DEREK: Is this really necessary?
Can't you just take the credit card
numbers and run that somehow?
No. This is very necessary.
Because right now
they could have
credit cards in your name,
take loans out.
They could have
your social security number.
They could commit crimes
in your name. Do you understand?
They can sell
this information to 20 more people.
This, this could
just be the beginning.
MIKE: It's amazing
how clueless people are.
It's like picking
your nose in the car
and you think
nobody's watching you.
And then they wonder
how in the world
someone got their
social security number.
JASON: You done with this?
MIKE: Yeah.
- Hey, Dad?
- What, babe?
You think maybe...
Maybe I could get an iPad?
My teacher said it would,
like, help with all my schoolwork.
(LAUGHS)
Really? I told you
I fixed the screen
on your laptop.
It's up in my office.
You don't need an iPad, bud.
What's this thing with you rolling your
eyes every time I say something?
Wrap that up good.
Way to go, butterfingers.
No chicken salad for lunch.
And clean the floor.
And don't use the dish rag.
(MUSIC THUMPING IN HOUSE)
COLE: Yeah,
so I got that same guy.
Keeps coming back on
with the lights turned off.
I can just see, like,
the shadow from his face on the thing.
It's, like, come on,
creeps me out. It's fucked up.
MALE: That's fucked up.
What's up, Kyle?
KYLE: Harvey,
this is Shane.
What's up, man?
He's that kid I met
at the skate park.
You hungry, Shane?
KYLE: Dig in.
COLE: He makes really
good fucking spaghetti.
- Dig in.
- It's my thing, spaghetti. I make spaghetti.
COLE: So, where you from?
Des Moines.
Yeah, you been on the streets?
Let the kid eat.
You know what
we do here, Shane?
How old are you?
SHANE: Um, 15.
Let me ask you a question.
Do you jerk off?
Yeah? You wanna
get paid for it?
- That would be fucking awesome.
KYLE: - Good, man.
One rule, Shane.
Trust me,
no one else. Okay?
SHANE: So, what am
I supposed to do?
MARIA: Take off your pants.
Just look cute.
They're dying for you to take it all off.
Now, play with
the toys over there.
Guys talk to you all at once
and your goal is to get them to go private.
And how long does
it take for someone to be interested?
Look, he's already got 14
that want to go private.
Look, this freak
wants to go C2C.
C2C is kinda gross
'cause you have to look right at them.
But cam to cam costs more
so if they wanna do it, you gotta do it.
Okay. All right.
Who is this guy?
MumboJumbo27.
- You feel good?
- Yeah, I feel good.
You just gotta do it.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
One nil! Big fuck you!
Fuck you.
Pick new teams.
All right. Let's do it again.
I'll beat you anyway, so...
- Dude. Holy shit.
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- He sent it.
I didn't think
he'd fucking do it.
He did it! He's butt naked!
- Oh, my God! What the fuck!
- He actually sent it.
He fucking wrote "love slave"
on his leg with lipstick!
Oh, my God.
That is fucking disgusting.
That's awesome.
It looks like a pink sausage!
This is so...
What, do you feel
sorry for him?
- No.
- Are you in love with him?
No, Frye.
Are you in wuv with him?
- Dude, stop.
- Are you in wuv with little Ben Boyd?
Gross, man!
I can feel your boner!
Okay, what I'd like
to tell people at this point is that...
I am not a marriage counselor.
I don't know what you two
know about each other, and that's okay.
I don't wanna know.
That being said, here's your CD
and a printed overview
of all suspicious activity.
Now, I think some
of your personal information
may have been retrieved with your
communications with fear&loathing.
What?
Who's fear&loathing?
It's just some guy.
He's in the chat room I go to.
All you would have
had to do was click on a link
or open an attachment from
him, and then he would've...
He would've installed
a Trojan virus onto your system.
Now, once he does this, he can do
anything he wants with your computer.
You log on, you punch in your
passwords, it comes up on his screen.
Everything you do, he can see.
He can turn on your camera.
He can watch you.
Who is fear&loathing?
Who's he?
How does he have my password?
Your password is your birthday.
And, Derek, gambling websites
are hacked all the time.
And you're also
corresponding with
the bank regarding
your second mortgage.
Wait, we don't have
a second mortgage.
Yeah.
And you received an e-mail
requesting additional information.
Now, banks would never ask for sensitive
information like that via email.
So, I think that's how he possibly got
your personal account numbers,
your social, your mother's maiden
name and all that other stuff.
Who is this guy?
What's his name?
The name I came up with
is Stephen Schumacher.
He's from Oakdale, PA.
- He told me his name was Finn.
- Yeah.
What I need to do now
is find proof. And then once I do that,
I need to contact the local PD in
Oakdale and bring them into it.
What kind of proof?
Bank receipts,
credit card statements.
If he makes any
large transaction, it could nail him.
All right.
And how long will that take?
Could take three weeks.
Could take three months.
We don't have three months.
The cops couldn't do
shit for us, that's why we hired you.
I understand that,
but it's just not that easy, Derek.
- You have to be patient.
- I'm patient. My bank's not patient.
I understand that,
but these people
use mail drops,
they use PO boxes.
They open an account one day,
they close it the next.
DEREK: Well, if you'll
excuse me, I gotta get back to work.
Don't want to lose my job, too.
I'm sorry you had
to see all this.
No, no, no.
Don't be sorry. It's okay.
I'm sorry to say
that I'm used to it.
Take that.
You been doing this long?
Privately, like 6 years.
I was a cop for 20 years.
Computer crimes unit.
My wife passed away,
so I retired
to spend some more
time with my kid. So.
I'm sorry.
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay,
I promise you.
It's in there.
He's gonna see everything in there.
I didn't, wasn't
really doing... I just...
NINA: You're just
going to look at me.
Okay.
You're gonna change
my voice for this, right?
NINA: Yeah.
My mom's boyfriend was a drunk.
Rager with a wicked left hook.
So, how did you end up here?
I met this guy at the mall.
He told me he could help me out,
give me a place to stay.
And then I got there and there were other
kids. it was just kind of chill.
He's really not a bad guy.
So, how does it work
in the house?
You know, some people
have built-in cameras on their laptops,
some have just webcams.
All of our stuff
is kinda streamed
through a site
that hosts everything.
And then they kinda,
like, take out a commission, I guess,
then just send us our checks.
I don't know, I mean, the younger you
look, then the more you make.
And what happens
when you outgrow it?
When you get older and you're too
old to bring in enough customers?
Um...
Do you think that
you'll do this forever?
I don't know.
I haven't really...
I haven't really
thought about that.
That's the guy!
Love slave!
STUDENTS: (CHANTING)
Love slave! Love slave!
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
LYDIA: Ben?
Hey.
You're home so early.
Is everything all right?
Yeah.
No band?
Canceled.
What are you doing?
Homework.
You okay, sweetie?
Yeah. I have a lot
of stuff to do.
All right.
Okay.
Why didn't you tell me money was
so tight with the second mortgage?
You know you'll
have to pick me up
and drop me off
every day, right?
I know.
I read it.
The whole thing.
You told him
everything about us.
I don't know what
you want from me.
You barely even
look at me anymore.
NINA: What time's your bus?
Kyle.
People are going to
smell it and come up.
No, we're gonna be fine.
Just loosen up. Here.
No!
Come on. One.
I did that whole
interview for you.
And so now I have to
repay you by getting stoned?
Just one hit.
One. I've not smoked
since 11th grade, so...
Just remember that.
I bet you were
a real bad girl back in high school, huh?
Nobody liked me in high school.
Surprising.
- Wow.
(SMOKE ALARM RINGS)
Oh, my God! I thought
I shut this off, Kyle.
That's loud.
Kyle, would you
fucking help me?
- Yeah, it's loud. Get a towel! Get a towel!
- Okay.
My God, they're gonna come in!
For God sakes!
Here.
- You could've just done that five minutes ago.
- Ow!
Oh, my God. You really
like bossing people around, don't you?
Let's play truth or dare.
Absolutely not.
Okay, great.
So, have you ever
cried over a pet?
Yes.
Who was it?
- Snowy.
(SCOFFS) Snowy?
Not an imaginative name,
I know, but she was a white rabbit.
She was very dear to me.
Did you do tricks with it?
Was it a magic rabbit?
How do you do tricks
with a rabbit?
Wow.
How do you do that in there?
- Give it a shot.
- I wanna try.
You just slow...
You don't force the smoke out.
Nothing's happening.
Mine's shit.
You know...
You're the first real
celebrity I've ever met.
Okay. Next question.
Have you ever...
Kissed a girl on the mouth?
I'm really hungry.
ABBY: It's awful.
GIRL: It's not that bad.
My hair is horrible.
So what? Okay, fine.
Smile looks fake.
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYS
IN NEXT ROOM)
Okay, then this one.
Don't post that picture.
Don't. I swear to God.
Could you turn it down!
(SCREAMS)
LYDIA: He's gonna wake up.
He's gonna...
He's gonna wake up.
Like, a lot of
the people look young
because that's really, like,
where the market is.
The younger you look,
the more you make.
Google the words "live webcam"
and the search will result
in countless sexually explicit sites,
not unlike the one
where Sam tells me
he gets hundreds of hits a day.
Sam wouldn't show me
the house, but says
that eight other kids,
or models as they're called,
live there with
a house manager.
You know, he's really
not that bad of a guy.
NINA: Imagine someone
recruiting runaways in your town
and creating
a child pornography ring.
Nina Dunham, WKGU, Channel 6.
(STAFF APPLAUDING)
MAN: - Way to go.
Nice job.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Kyle?
You were great.
You couldn't tell it was you, right?
I kept my promise.
Listen, I'm gonna
go out for a drink with some people here.
- So, can I call you back later?
- Nice work.
I wish you were here
to celebrate.
MOVER 1: You got that
by yourself?
MOVER 2: Okay,
pass it up here.
Shit, Derek, I'm sorry.
Thanks for going
out of your way, man.
Already sending guys, huh?
I've been late on
those things for months.
Fucking repo guys.
Here's the rest of it.
I appreciate it.
Next time, don't open the door.
They can't take anything
unless you open the door.
So, when do you think
the cops are gonna question this guy?
It's like I said,
these cops, they're swamped.
They don't have the resources.
It's like, 25,000 people
a day get their identity stolen, so...
Take a ticket.
And what about you?
We got his name,
we got his address.
Can you go take care
of this son of a bitch?
Derek.
I'm a detective, not a hitman.
Well, I mean...
I mean, question him,
of course.
Like I said,
my guys at Cybercrime are tracking him.
They can't do anything
without concrete proof. Concrete proof.
So I'm supposed to
just sit here and watch
while things go to shit?
What would you do?
You don't wanna know
what I would do.
I would strangle
the son of a bitch.
But that's not what
I'm saying for you to do.
(TRUCK ENGINE STARTS)
You know what,
take this payment back.
- It's your money.
- Take the money. You'll give it to me later.
You may need it.
Thanks.
I saw everything.
I know about your boy,
and I'm so sorry.
But you cannot let
this bullshit break you.
You hear me?
You stay strong, brother.
Cin, no one's helping us.
No one's ever gonna help us.
I'm gonna find that guy myself.
I'll fix this.
I wanna come.
Yeah, that's right.
B-O-Y-D. Boyd, Rich Boyd.
The school's my next call.
Uh-huh. Great, thank you.
Please do, quickly.
They're gonna have
a cop call me.
Okay.
Well, I'm still gonna go.
Can I please speak to the Principal,
Headmaster's Office, please?
Dude, we're gonna get caught.
We used a fake e-mail, man.
Dude, just give me your iPad
and I'll delete the profile.
Use your phone.
My dad has software
that would totally wipe it.
Just let me have it.
I have to go.
- Can I please have it?
- Fine, all right?
- Thanks. Bye, dude.
- Don't fuck it up!
KYLE: You ever think about
what you're gonna do, like, when you're 20?
MARIA: Be famous.
Yeah, for what?
I don't know. Maybe I'll be on
a reality show, or something.
You'll open up US Weekly
and I'll be there
in the "Stars that
are just like us" page.
Mm-hmm.
You should take
a right at the exit.
Okay.
All right, this is McClean.
What number was it?
Um, number 418.
DEREK: There, red one.
CINDY: So, we're just
gonna sit here?
Yeah. We just wait.
And we'll watch him,
you know, come and go.
Rich.
I'm right here.
Can we go?
Are you ready to go to the hospital?
I'm gonna stay.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to figure out
what he could have been thinking.
Well, me too.
Can you bring it?
I don't want him to wake up
and we're not there.
I feel like he may have
deleted a few things.
I want to bring
this blanket because...
I don't want him to be cold.
It's so cold in there.
Hey.
Honey.
Meet you there.
PETER: Hey, Nina!
- What's up?
- I got a call from CNN.
Their office saw your piece,
they wanna put it in a special.
You're kidding.
No. Nice job.
- Hey, look.
- At what?
Beamer pulling in.
Very nice fucking car.
Yeah.
There he is.
(STARTS ENGINE)
Is that him?
CINDY: Yeah,
just 20 years later.
Did you send him pictures, too?
I'm such an idiot.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
LYDIA: You know what?
You need to take a shower.
We're meeting
the neurologist at 10:00 a.m.
Did you know that
his favorite book was White Noise?
No, I didn't.
What?
What is it, Abby?
- Marnie's younger sister is in his grade...
- Oh, my God.
And she said she got it.
Oh, my God! Oh, Jesus.
- What the hell's this?
- I don't know. I just got it.
- Who sent that to you? Why do you have it?
- Marnie sent it to me.
Has everybody in the school seen it?
I don't know!
I'm sure everyone saw it!
FRYE: What do you mean, you're
chatting with the dad? Are you insane?
Dude, I'm dealing.
It's just not that simple.
Why are you talking to him?
Just, hey.
Delete the fucking account
and give me back the iPad.
Dude, if I ignore him...
If I ignore him
or I delete Jess's account right away...
I mean, how would that look?
She would be the only suspect.
We just have to act chill and lay low.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(ALL TOASTING INDISCERNIBLY)
I always knew you'd outgrow us.
Yeah, right.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
- Oh.
It's me.
Hey, Kyle.
Hey, what's up?
I think I'm here.
Here where?
I think I'm downstairs.
Downstairs?
I came to celebrate. We're
celebrating, right?
Um...
Yeah. Sure.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
- ...he would trust me.
- Did you give him your address?
I had to, Peter.
- What are you doing?
- How else...
I had to make him trust me.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
KYLE: Hey. What's up?
Kyle, this is Peter.
Hey, Peter, how's it going, man?
Wow, this is an amazing view!
You're okay with this?
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
It's fine.
We're fine, buddy.
You can take a hike.
I'm just kidding. It's a joke.
Nina, you call me if you need me.
Of course. All right.
- Hey...
- All right. Bye. Go.
It's not bad.
Peter seems like a lot of fun.
Do you read all these books?
These all yours?
Not all of them.
So, how did you get here?
I caught a bus.
It's crazy, right?
This is a...
It's a beautiful bedroom.
It's very nice.
Well, I like it.
It's firm.
The couch is firm, also.
You know, I've been...
I've been thinking
a lot about what you said...
About the future
and everything.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, do you think
you might wanna leave Harvey?
Kinda, yeah.
Yeah, but I don't have
anywhere else to go.
Sure you do.
Like where?
I don't know. You can walk
into a youth center or a church...
Church?
Yeah, that's a really great fucking idea.
Go to a church. I hear
it's a perfect place for young dudes to go.
Kyle, it's late,
I'm just spitballing.
It doesn't have to be a church.
Fuck it. I should go to MickeyD's.
I could be someone's bitch.
Make some fucking burgers,
pack some groceries.
A really excellent idea,
you got there.
(SMACKS HER BUTT)
(SCOFFS) Whoa.
What is this?
What the hell is this thing?
That, I will have you know,
is an award that I received
- for reporting on an annual charity drive.
- Wait.
- Do your voice.
- What voice?
Your reporter voice. Come on, let's hear it.
Where you get really serious.
Come on, I rode a bus for,
like, four hours, and it was really smelly.
- All right.
- I wanna hear the voice.
I'll show you the walk-and-talk.
Walk-and-talk,
that sounds very official.
Well, John,
I'm here outside of downtown
where, earlier today,
a swarm of Africanized bees
terrorized the community.
And then, John...
Officials say that one of the reporters
had this massive, crazy urge
to have some awesomely amazing sex.
And later on, it was reported
that that was actually total crap.
- Tickle? A little?
- Slightly.
- Ticklish? Are we ticklish?
- No! I'm not!
I can see that.
Um...
I have to be up really early.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna put this back.
DEREK: Pays someone
to do his laundry.
- Must be nice.
- Yeah.
He works there?
Wait here.
What are you doing?
Be careful!
- Hi.
- Hey, I lost my ticket.
Last name?
McNeil.
It's not in the system.
It's a blue polo.
No, it's not here.
You sure?
Yeah.
That's weird.
What do you think happened to it?
Think it got stolen?
Something like that?
You ever get robbed?
I'm just asking.
I used to work retail,
so I know that that
happens sometimes.
I would always keep a gun
under the counter, when I worked retail.
Do you do that?
Do you have a gun here?
Do I know you?
No.
I'm just making chit-chat.
Next?
- Sorry.
- Just two items?
What's your name?
Where's Dad?
Who knows.
I haven't seen him all day.
Don't leave me alone with them.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
- Hey, Jana.
- Hey.
It's Kendall Media,
they need you.
Something at
one of their stations.
Not now.
Tell them to get somebody else, please.
They asked for you.
What's this about? Why?
The FBI just showed up
at one of their stations.
All right.
ROBERTA: We need you
to give up the kid's address.
I'm not exactly sure
of what you want me to say
because I can't give
you that information.
I'm pretty sure
that you know that.
Sources are protected.
ROBERTA: I understand that, but a
serious crime has been committed here.
These kids are victims.
They are coerced, seduced.
Some of them are 14,
15 years old.
And NCMEC flagged
this site a year ago
and the host server's offshore.
Untouchable.
So, of course,
when we saw your piece on CNN,
it's an opening, we have to go for it.
But, you see, I can't betray
his trust like that. I can't.
Besides, I don't even
know where he lives. I don't know.
I don't have a cell phone number.
He uses prepaid cell phones.
- He's not stupid.
- How did you find him?
Well, I was looking into a story
on teen runaways,
and if you Google that,
you get some weird stuff.
So you befriended him.
Did you pay to talk to him?
Or buy him anything?
Give him money?
News organizations
don't pay their sources.
- Is that true, Ms. Dunham?
- Of course that's true.
There's just these charges
on your PayPal account.
The initial payments are
having access, private access,
to talking with the boy.
And the additions are
an option the client has to encourage
the youth to spend
more time talking to them.
Okay.
So, by way of gifting them...
- "Gifting"?
- So you gave him gifts.
NINA: These weren't
personal gifts.
No, no, I understand.
Why don't we go
have a talk in the other room?
No, I can explain myself to her.
It's not a problem.
I just wanna know
what the relationship is with the boy.
Come on. Now, in my office.
I want to understand.
Were you intimate with him?
Did you have sex with him?
RICH: - Don't answer that.
- Nina.
Absolutely not.
RICH: Look, I represent
the interest of the parent company.
If you want to make a First Amendment
case out of this, be my guest,
but you will need another attorney.
As far as I'm concerned,
you need to give them whatever they want.
I would also recommend
that you suspend her immediately.
I know that I have to suspend her.
I know that, Rich.
That's way too much!
This is not too much, Nina.
You crossed a line.
This kid came to your fucking house!
What was I supposed to
do about that, Peter?
He showed up, okay, and I didn't want him
to feel like I had used him.
Since when do you care what a source feels
like after you get what you want, huh?
Excuse me. I gotta go.
- Um, how long?
RICH: - What's that?
The suspension?
Well...
Until you give those two Federal Agents you
just tried to lie to the info they want.
CINDY: You know what
this reminds of?
Sitting in my Corolla,
waiting for you
outside the barracks,
wondering when you'd come out.
It reminds me of sitting
outside this shithole called Al-Qa'im.
Nine guys packed into an LAV.
It was the start of the war,
so we were pretty buttoned up.
I had to pee in water bottles.
And at one point, Gunny Mullin wanted
to stitch up a couple of hadjis
'cause they kept, like,
driving back and forth in front of us,
but the call never came.
You remember Mullin, right?
From Lejeune?
Good guy, like, a long torso?
What is it?
It's just, you never
talk about this stuff.
(CAR ALARM CHIRPING)
Right. Stay here.
Stay, stay, stay.
Derek, be careful.
(WHISPERING) I don't think
we should do this. This doesn't feel right.
CINDY: What am I looking for?
Any proof.
Receipts, bank statements.
- Cindy.
- What is it?
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
CINDY: Shit!
- Oh, God! We gotta get out of here.
- Go.
CINDY: Leave it! Let's go!
Go, go, go.
Sonny boy, doing your homework?
- That's what I'm doing now.
- Yeah? Good.
Where'd you get that?
That's Frye's.
He left it here on accident.
- On accident?
- Yeah.
- You're not on it?
- No.
(TABLET CHIMES)
Hmm.
Your computer time
is over tonight.
Really?
Really? Really?
Stay off it. Put it here.
Do your work.
All right. I'm doing it.
Don't make me be the bad guy.
KYLE: Hey, what's going on?
NINA: Hey, thanks for
calling me back. I want...
Hold on one second.
I'm just running out of the house.
So, have you given any thought
to what we talked about the other day?
What about? Like the future?
Yeah... I meant what I said.
I wanna help you.
Maybe, you know,
go to school or...
I'd like to help you get on your feet.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And I know you think that
Harvey's a decent guy, and I understand,
'cause he took care of you.
But here's the thing,
he's using you to recruit minors.
And that's a felony.
Really? It's a felony?
Yeah. Recruiting minors
could get you serious jail time.
So, what do you want me to do?
- You wanna get me outta here?
- Yeah.
Just say the word
and I'll come and get you.
I can come get you now,
if you want.
You want my address?
How else are you gonna
move all of your stuff?
All that shit that
everybody buys you.
Um, look, can I think about it?
Yeah, just call me.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
You are, yes. No, you're the
same detective I spoke to, sir.
R-H-O-N-Y.
Yes, I'll hold.
No, no, no. You don't have
somebody from Legal call me.
I am a lawyer, okay?
I'll subpoena you. Do you understand me?
Now, this is your website,
you work with me.
The profile name
is Jessica Rhony.
R-H-O-N-Y.
What's happening?
Hey.
MAN: We'll have someone
get in touch with you.
Yeah, as soon as you can.
Rich.
What are you doing?
Hang on. R-H-O-N-Y.
- H-O-R-N-Y.
- What?
"Horny." Hang on a second,
is this a fucking anagram?
- Is this a fucking joke?
- You know what?
You need to pull it together.
I don't even know
what that means, Lydia.
Let the cops do their job.
- And you can do yours.
- They can do theirs.
What are you talking about?
I'm his father. I'm looking for answers.
- Don't you give a shit what's going on?
- No, no, no.
Don't you tell me how to handle this.
You don't get to tell
me how to handle this.
Then don't tell me how to handle it.
Ben is down there and you're in here.
Right. Doing my job.
You're down there doing your job.
You're stroking his hair,
you're whispering to him. That's great!
I can't do that. I'm doing this.
This girl might not exist.
What, so you have someone to blame?
And then, is he gonna wake up?
ABBY: He just lies there.
And every once in
a while something moves,
but they say it's just an impulse.
My parents are totally imploding.
What do the doctors say?
Oh, my God!
He invited me to Danny's.
- Oh!
- What should I say?
- What are you gonna say? "Yes"?
- I don't know.
Say yes.
But I don't know.
What?
I got a bank account statement.
Yeah?
Yeah. Looks like we got a check here
for $4,700, and another one for $3,950.
Okay. Does it say what it's for?
He's probably paying off his mortgage
on our dime.
Look at this.
Pay-Per-View charge.
Adult entertainment, $59.
- In one month?
- In one month.
I knew he was a creep.
What do you think it's for?
Children of the Cornhole?
(LAUGHS)
Sperms of Endearment.
I'm gonna confront this guy, Cindy.
When he's least expecting it,
I'm gonna go to his house. I'll walk up,
I'll knock on the door,
and I'm just gonna say,
"What's up? What's going on?
Have you seen our money?"
"We kind of miss our money."
I'll just talk to him a bit, man to man.
I mean, you never know
what he could be like.
I'll be fine.
And if something goes wrong,
I brought my M9.
You brought your gun?
It's not gonna get to that.
I'm just gonna scare him a little.
People like this,
they need to be scared sometimes.
And that's my job.
I'm gonna scare him.
(INAUDIBLE)
(MACHINES BEEPING)
RICH: Hey. How you doing?
Sorry.
You know Ben?
Yeah, from school.
Really nice of you to come.
What's your name? I'm Rich.
- Mike.
- How you doing?
Come on in. You guys close?
You know, Mike,
let me ask you question?
He ever mention anybody named Jessica?
- Jessica?
- Yeah. He ever talk about her?
No.
Come on in. Grab a chair.
I actually gotta get going.
No, no, stay. I mean,
not because of me. Just stay.
Maybe I can buy you a soda or something.
Let me buy you a soda.
I want a coffee.
Good coffee upstairs.
Come on.
Okay.
He goes to the gym?
Really?
Well, we were there,
but we were just kind of messing around.
Sounds more like it.
What else? Anything?
What's he do for fun?
- For fun?
- Yeah.
You guys ever do anything crazy?
I mean, we blow stuff up sometimes.
- Really?
- Yeah, I mean, we lit these little firecrackers,
and then we'd take
all our little army parachute figures,
and we'd go to a building
and then threw it out the window.
And it would blow up while it was
still floating down to the bottom.
It was crazy.
I should go. My dad kind of
gets mad when I'm late, so...
Okay.
Thanks.
You come by any time you want.
- All right?
- Okay.
(BEN VOCALIZING MELODY
ON LAPTOP)
(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
You guys said you'd protect him
if I gave you his address.
ROBERTA: Yeah, I promise you.
This is for his own good.
NINA: I can't have
anything happen to him.
Don't worry,
we do this every day.
Social Services will be on hand.
When are you gonna go in?
It's a few days or a week for a warrant.
What? A week?
Are you sure that this is the best idea?
Trust me. Listen. Listen.
What you've done is a really good thing,
Ms. Dunham.
- Right.
- You did good.
Right. Well, thank you.
Work it, God.
Just hurry up.
I'm trying.
These fuckers put you through hell.
All right. All right. Reason...
JASON: Hurry up.
FRYE: I'm trying, man.
Takes a long time.
You have to e-mail them and...
You have to give a reason.
I don't feel safe online.
Hey, boys.
Oh, hey.
We were just looking for a power cord
for Frye's iPad.
FRYE: I gotta charge it.
Top right drawer.
- Got it. Thanks.
MIKE: - Got it?
Hey, fellas!
You guys wanna tell me
what you were doing up in my office?
Told you, we were just
getting a power cord.
Right, you were looking for a power cord
for his iPad.
Frye, let me ask you a question.
'Cause you're a smart kid, right?
Yeah.
Do I look as stupid to
you as I do to Jason?
No, sir.
Look close.
- No. You don't.
- No?
Frye, you wanna tell me what
you were doing in my office?
- It was just...
- Frye.
Frye.
It was supposed to be a joke.
- What?
- Dude, shut up.
No, you shut up. What did you say?
We were just trying to mess with him.
What did you say?
It was supposed to be a joke.
We didn't think he'd hurt himself.
What? Wait, wait, whoa...
Who were you messing with?
Are talking about that Boyd kid?
You had something to do with that?
Did you have something to do that?
Yes.
"Yes." Yes?
Oh, man.
You wanna fuck with somebody, you do it
to their face, you hear me, tough guy?
Yeah, like you?
Like me?
You, go home.
Go home, Frye!
Don't you touch that. Get outta here.
This is bad. You are in big trouble.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You're sorry? What are you sorry for?
'Cause I caught you?
Or you're sorry 'cause there's a father
wondering if his son is gonna wake up?
Jason, get up.
Get up, get up, get up!
Go to your room. Get outta my sight.
I am so happy your mother
is not with us to see any of this.
I am...
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Do you know what that father's
going through right now
'cause of what you did to his son?
Do you know what you did?
Say something! Say something!
I know that father!
He's nothing like you!
MARIA: Kyle, wake up! Wake up!
Yo, let's hurry up, dude.
What the fuck's going on?
Harvey said the house is gonna get raided.
BOY: Hurry up!
Fuck!
MARIA: Ken, just hold on!
Get my bags.
I'm leaving this house
in five fucking seconds!
Coming.
Come on, go, let's go.
HARVEY: I don't know
what fucking happened.
Just had to get the fuck outta there.
Probably one of the fucking kids.
I find out who it is, you can have 'em.
I'll be crossing the state line
in about 20 fucking minutes
or something.
I don't know. What?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
WOMAN: Field office.
Yeah, extension 2221.
NINA: What the hell's going on?
He just texted me
saying they're moving.
We didn't do anything.
He must've tipped them off.
How would he tip them off?
He didn't know.
You promised you'd get him out safely.
Did he say where they were going?
Of course he didn't say where...
How's he supposed to know
where they're going?
Yeah, hello? Fuck!
Fucking battery.
Give me your phone, Kyle.
Kyle, give me your phone.
- Give me your fucking phone!
- Okay.
NINA: He could be in trouble.
You've got to move in!
It just doesn't work like that, honey.
What way does it work?
If you can get him to cooperate,
we can try to help him.
Right, well,
thank you for your help.
Fuck!
Get your stuff. Let's go.
Hey, Harvey, can I get my phone back?
Come on.
Thanks.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Kyle! God almighty, there you are!
- I was so worried about you.
- Hey, look.
Some crazy shit's going down right now.
Where are you?
About an hour outside town.
Some place called Saw Mill River Motel.
Kyle, listen to me. After my story aired,
the FBI came to see me.
Are you kidding me?
What are you talking about, the FBI?
- They threatened me.
- Did you give them our address?
It wasn't supposed to happen this way.
I don't fucking believe this!
You straight up lied to me!
Kyle, listen to me.
You were never even coming, were you?
Yes! Of course I was coming! I was coming.
You don't give a fuck about me!
No, no, no, no.
Of course I do! I'll come get you now.
Fuck that.
Kyle? Kyle!
Fuck!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- So, you really wanna do this tonight?
- Yeah.
You nervous?
Yeah.
That's adrenaline.
It's good. Makes you feel alive.
Let's just go for it, okay?
Okay.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Lantos. Yeah, what's up?
Right.
LYDIA: Abby said you went
to the hospital today.
Yeah.
His friend came by today. Nice kid.
Who?
Mike.
- Mike. Seemed like a nice guy.
- Mike?
You mean Marcus? His old friend, Marcus?
I don't know any Mike.
- You don't know a Mike?
- No.
What?
Damn it! I knew there was
something off about that kid!
What are you talking about?
- This Mike guy.
- What about him?
I just need a last name.
Dad, what are you doing?
- Losing it.
- No, I'm not.
What's going on?
LYDIA: Honey, I'll be there in a minute.
RICH: Where's his goddamn year?
I need you to calm down.
I'm gonna show you Jessica.
Oh, my God.
Who gives a shit about Jessica!
All you care about is making yourself
feel less guilty!
I'm the one who cut him down!
And I knew that he didn't have any friends!
LYDIA: It's not your fault.
- I didn't do anything!
- It's not your fault.
ABBY: And people made fun of him!
I got him.
LYDIA: It's not your fault.
Lydia...
It's not even Mike.
It's not even his name.
HARVEY: I thought, probably give him
some crazy gift or something like that.
FEMALE MODEL: All right,
maybe I'll consider it.
HARVEY: Yeah, go look at them.
You'll have to split the thing with me.
We could arrange something.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Are the cops here?
No! I'm alone. I came to get you.
You shouldn't be here right now.
I don't blame you for not believing me,
but I promise you, Kyle,
I promise I came alone.
Please, just get in the car.
I can make this right.
(NINA SPEAKING INDISCERNIBLY)
If I go inside and I
fucking get all my shit
and I pack it all up,
I need to know that I can stay with you.
Let's get your stuff and we'll talk...
No, it's a yes or no.
It's a simple question,
can I stay with you?
I don't know! Why do we need...
What do you mean, you don't know?
I'm not sure. Because...
What?
Because you're so much younger than me
and I don't know whether it's a good idea.
Oh.
Wow.
Why can't we just go
and we can talk about it on the way?
Kyle, please.
If I wasn't? If I wasn't younger?
Then, would you want me there?
- Forget this.
- Forget what? Kyle!
- Kyle!
(HORN HONKS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Mike, how are you?
Hey, Derek. Yeah, it's not him.
It's not him. My guy, Lantos,
got Schumacher's IP address
and turns out he's a victim, too.
What do you mean?
Someone was using his computer as a proxy,
all right?
I don't know, we're tracing it from Texas.
Anyway, the bottom line is,
Schumacher is not your guy.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I just got the information.
Now, I don't know where you are, brother,
but you gotta stand down. You hear me?
Derek?
I got it. It's okay. It's all right.
I gotta jump. I'll be in touch.
Thank you.
CINDY: What did he say?
It's not him.
Derek, please. It's okay, babe.
Derek, I don't care about the money.
Or the house.
Please, just take me home.
I was a Marine, Cindy.
What am I now?
I'm a tool.
Some paper-pushing grunt.
- No.
- Yeah.
(RINGS DOORBELL)
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, my name's Rich Boyd.
Your son put my son in the hospital
and I wanna talk to him right now.
His name's Jason.
- I don't have time for...
- Sometimes he's Jessica.
He's got a little bit
of an identity crisis.
He harassed my son.
He's sadistic. He needs fucking help.
- He needs fucking help?
- Yeah.
- My son needs help?
Your kid tried to hang himself
and my kid needs help?
You knew? You fucking knew!
Shut the car down. Get out. Get out.
Come on, get out! Step out slowly.
Come on, get out!
I'm coming. Take it easy.
You stay in the car.
Stay right there.
- What is this? Huh?
- What are you talking about?
You're following me. You're stalking me.
You come into my business.
You break into my house.
Do you think I'm stupid or something?
NINA: Just come with me!
No, just leave me alone.
Get your stuff and let's go!
What is wrong with you?
Seriously, what the fuck is wrong with you!
Do you have any idea what you've done?
No. Not just to me, to all my friends,
to Harvey!
You think Harvey exploits me?
I like what I do! Do you get that?
I don't wanna be saved from this!
I turn people on, so what?
You couldn't turn a fucking light on,
you know that?
You're the one who exploits people.
You exploited me!
You...
You're the one who fucking exploits people.
I'm fucking done.
Okay, okay.
KYLE: I'm not gonna listen.
You get the fuck away from me.
Let's talk about it.
No, we're not gonna
fucking talk about it.
DEREK: - What's your plan?
- Don't move.
- Shoot me in front of my wife?
- Stay right there.
- The safety's on.
- Shut up!
Steven? It's Cindy Hull.
Cindy?
Derek!
Dad!
(JASON GRUNTING)
You Okay?
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
CINDY: Stop, stop, stop.
DEREK: You do this a lot?
You send a lot of married women
your picture?
- Can we talk here?
- Derek, stop.
DEREK: - How does it feel?
- It was a mistake.
Yeah, we're gonna keep going.
Have you ever had a gun
in your face before?
- I have.
CINDY: - Derek, he didn't do anything.
He did.
Don't do this.
Please tell him
it was harmless, Cindy.
Derek, it's not his fault. It's my fault.
What are you talking about?
He talked to me...
When you wouldn't.
He told me about taking
his wife to chemo...
And how cold her hands were,
and the meds.
And I told him about...
And I told him about... Ethan.
I told him about our little baby boy.
(DEREK SOBBING)
It's okay. Please, baby.
Come on, give me the gun.
(EXHALES)
Just leave her. It's fine. Let's go.
(NINA COUGHING)
(VEHICLE STARTING)
Oh, my God!
I'm okay.
- No, you're not.
- I'll explain. Just let me...
I love you.
I love you, too.
Everything...
Everything that I love
is in this room.
(SOBBING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(MACHINE BEEPING STEADILY)